gloodu.com 2015-12-13

# Privacy Policy - HD video mania

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url www.google.com/privacy/ads/ Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, GloOdu.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting GloOdu.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of GloOdu.com then you may contact us at admin@gloodu.com

**Copyright © 2015[HD video mania](http://gloodu.com/) | [DMCA](http://gloodu.com/dmca-notice)**   
Disclaimer : All contents are copyrighted and owned by their respected owners. HD video mania does not upload or host any videos / musics / images file on this server. HD video mania only links to user submitted websites and is not responsible for third party website content. It is illegal for you to distribute copyrighted files without permission. Downloads must be for time-shifting, non-commercial, personal, private use only. Thanks for visitor, yahoo.com, google.com, bing.com, youtube.com and advertiser.   
All content posted by our users is [dedicated to the public domain](http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/)  

**CERTAIN CONTENT THAT APPEARS ON THIS SITE COMES FROM AMAZON SERVICES LLC. THIS CONTENT IS PROVIDED 'AS IS' AND IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE OR REMOVAL AT ANY TIME.**  
This site is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com, endless.com, myhabit.com, smallparts.com, or amazonwireless.com. Some content that appears on this site come from AMAZON Services LLC This content is provided 'as' and are subject to change or remove it at any time. Amazon, the Amazon logo, Endless, and the Endless logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.
